Home
---------
Kills bacteria and germs. Provides a pleasant and relaxing aroma. Eliminates radon that can cause lung cancer.

Radon is a radioactive, colorless, odorless, tasteless noble gas. Unlike all the other intermediate elements in the aforementioned decay chains, radon is, under normal conditions, gaseous and easily inhaled. Radon gas is a health hazard. It is often the single largest contributor to an individual's background radiation dose. According to the United States Environmental Protection Agency, radon is the second most frequent cause of lung cancer, after cigarette smoking, causing 21,000 lung cancer deaths per year in the United States. About 2,900 of these deaths occur among people who have never smoked.


Hotel
---------
Our product can make your customer stay even better. Keeping a room fresh when new people always come and go is very hard. Even air refresheners can't handle it. Our product will eliminate all the unpleasant odor and sanitize the room without any harm to your guests (Most of cleaning chemicals include bad ingredients that are not good/safe for humans).

Hospital
-----------
Many people get sick or have various diseases, so they go to hospital to see a doctor and get a cure. This is what makes hospital a dangerous place to stay at. There are too many sick people and they spread all kind of bacteria and germs very quickly. And even thouth there are many sanitizers, it is still not enough. Phytoncide can add extra security and peace of mind, as well as nice, forest smell that can be benefical in many ways.


Kindergarten
------------------
Young kids are always curious and want to explore everything. They don't care about hygiene at all. They touch dirty objects from class room or outside and then touch themselves with dirty hands. And it makes them an easy victim to bacteria and germs. With Phytonchide parents can feel safe about their kids. Our phytonchide product will kill germs and bacteria and add pleasant forest smell that can improve brain concentration (scientific proof).


New Car
------------
There are over 200 chemical compounds found in vehicles. Since these chemicals are not regulated, consumers have no way of knowing the dangers they face. Benzene, toluene, formaldehyde, and heavy metals are all part of the mix. Immediate symptoms can range from a sore throat to headaches, dizziness, allergic reactions and nausea, depending on the sensitivity of an individual. Continued exposure to some of these can lead to hormonal disruption, reproductive impacts and damage to the liver, kidneys and central nervous system — or even cancer. Our phytonchide product can eliminate most of these bad chemicals, thus protect your health condition.


